raisingcanes.com 2016-11-29

# Privacy Statement | Raising Cane's | Chicken Fingers | Cane's Sauce

Raising Cane’s USA, LLC (hereinafter referred to as either, “The Company”, “We”, “Us” or “Our”) is committed to protecting the privacy of personal information you may provide Us on this website (the “Site”). We believe it is important for you to know how We treat your personal information. We updated this Privacy Policy effective as of 3/17/2015. The terms of this Privacy Policy apply to all users of this Site. If you do not agree with the terms of this Privacy Policy, you should immediately cease the use of this Site. Below you will find answers to several questions regarding Our revised Privacy Policy.

  * What information does the Company collect about me on this Site?
  * What does the Company do with the information collected?
  * With whom does the Company share the information?
  * How can I stop receiving notices about future offers or to stop my Personal Information from being shared with third parties?
  * How do I correct or update my Personal Information?
  * How does the Company protect the security of my Personal Information?
  * Does the Company’s Site link to other sites?
  * What is the effective date of the Company Privacy Policy and how will the Company notify me of changes to its Privacy Policy?
  * How does the Company handle children’s privacy online?
  * How do I contact the Company?
  * What is your Mobile Privacy Policy?

#### 1\. What information does the Company collect about me on this Site?

The Company collects personally identifiable information that you may voluntarily provide on online forms, which may include: user registration, sweepstakes registration, contact requests, guest comments, online surveys, and other online activities. The personally identifiable information (“Personal Information”) collected on this Site can include some or all of the following: your name, address, telephone number, e-mail addresses, credit card information, demographic information, and any other information you may voluntarily provide. You will have the choice whether or not to disclose such Personal Information in the above activities; however, some parts of the Site and some services may be more difficult or impossible to use if you choose not to disclose Personal Information.

At the time of registration, you will have the option to receive future offers and updates from the Company by checking the appropriate opt-in box. If you choose to opt-in, your Personal Information will be kept in a secured database and We will alert you via e-mail to new features, special offers, updated information and new services.

In addition to the Personal Information identified above, Our web servers automatically identify computers by their IP addresses. The Company may use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the Site, track users’ movement and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. To emphasize, IP addresses are not linked to Personal Information.

Further, Our Site may use technologies such as “cookies” to provide visitors with tailored information upon each visit. Cookies are a common part of many commercial websites that allow small text files to be sent by a website, accepted by a web browser and then placed on your hard drive as recognition for repeat visits to the Site. Every time you visit Our Site, Our servers, through cookies, pixels and/or GIF files, collect basic technical information such as your domain name, the address of the last URL visited prior to clicking through to the Site, and your browser and operating system. You do not need to enable cookies to visit Our Site; however, some parts of the Site and some services may be more difficult or impossible to use if cookies are disabled. To emphasize, cookies are not linked to any Personal Information while on this Site.

BACK TO TOP

#### 2\. What does the Company do with the information collected?

The Company may use your Personal Information for any of the following purposes: (1) to understand the use of the Site and make improvements; (2) to fulfill prizes; (3) to register visitors for online activities such as: online ordering, sweepstakes, contests, surveys, employment applications, comment forms, or any other online interactive activities; (4) to respond to specific requests from visitors; (5) to obtain parental consent from visitors under 18 years of age, when necessary; (6) to provide any necessary notices to visitors or their parent or legal guardians if situations prompt such notification; (7) to protect the security or integrity of the Site if necessary; 8) to send notices of special promotions, offers or solicitations; and (9) in general, to promote and market the Company’s business and various products.

BACK TO TOP

#### 3\. With whom does the Company share the information?

Raising Cane’s System includes Raising Cane’s USA, LLC, The Company may share Personal Information collected on this Site with any affiliate or subsidiaries and any other future subsidiaries or affiliates. The Company will not sell, rent, loan, transfer, or otherwise disclose any Personal Information to third parties except as set forth in this statement. The Company may share Personal Information with third parties under the following circumstances: (i) in connection with a court order, subpoena, government investigation, or when otherwise required by law; (ii) in the event of a corporate sale, merger, acquisition, or similar event; or (iii) working with third party companies to support the Site’s technical operation or execute a specific promotion or program (such as providing responses to the Guest Comments Page, conduct surveys, or maintain a database of visitor information, etc.).

If Personal Information is shared with any third party for the purposes of executing a specific promotion or program, it will be clearly communicated to visitors that the third party will have no right to use the Personal Information for independent purposes. In support of this policy, the Company will enter into written agreements with any third party receiving Personal Information requiring the third party to comply with the Company’s privacy policies and applicable laws. To avoid your Personal Information from being shared with a third party, you can choose not to use the affected service or participate in the affected promotional activity.

BACK TO TOP

#### 4\. How can I stop receiving notices about future offers or to stop my Personal Information from being shared with third parties?

Users, who initially opted-in to receive future offers or promotional materials, or to allow the sharing of Personal Information with third parties, may subsequently opt-out by sending an e-mail to [heycanes@raisingcanes.com](mailto:heycanes@raisingcanes.com). The Company will implement the change within seven days of your request. The Company will send an acknowledgement or confirmation of the request to the e-mail address on file.

BACK TO TOP

#### 5\. How do I correct or update my Personal Information?

You control the accuracy of your Personal Information. If your Personal Information changes, feel free to correct, update or delete/deactivate it by e-mailing [heycanes@raisingcanes.com](mailto:heycanes@raisingcanes.com). If you wish to review your Personal Information that the Company has on record, you may contact [heycanes@raisingcanes.com](mailto:heycanes@raisingcanes.com).

BACK TO TOP

#### 6\. How does the Company protect the security of my Personal Information?

The Company uses appropriate security measures to protect all Personal Information collected in a secure, controlled environment. In addition, the Company configures the list server software to refuse to divulge the e-mail addresses of the list subscribers to anyone other than authorized the Company staff members, including other list subscribers. In the event of a security breach whereas your Personal Information is acquired by an unauthorized person, the Company will take appropriate steps to contain the breach and to notify you of the unauthorized acquisition.

BACK TO TOP

#### 7\. Does the Company’s Site link to other sites?

Yes. This Site may contain links to other websites that may not be owned or operated by the Company. The Company cannot control nor is responsible for the privacy practices or content of such other websites. The Company encourages you to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This Privacy Policy applies solely to Personal Information collected on this Site.

BACK TO TOP

#### 8\. What is the effective date of the Company’s Privacy Policy and how will the Company notify me of changes to its Privacy Policy?

This Privacy Policy was last updated on November 17th, 2008. The Company will post any changes on the Site’s Homepage, so visitors are always aware of any changes to what information We collect, how We use it, and under what circumstances We disclose it. If We decide to use your Personal Information in a manner different than first communicated, the Company will notify users by e-mail to the e-mail addresses on record. Users will then be given a choice as to whether or not their Personal Information can be used in the new manner.

In the event that the Company goes through a business transition, such as a merger, another company acquires the Company or its Affiliates, or the Company sells a portion of its assets, your personal information will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred. Thirty days prior to the change of ownership or control, you will be informed of this exchange and its effects via prominent notice on Our site. If as a result of a business transition, your personally identifiable information will be used in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection, you will be give the choice to opt-out.

BACK TO TOP

#### 9\. How does the Company handle children’s privacy online?

The Company adheres to the federal privacy protection standards articulated in the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA).

On the sections directed towards children, the Company does not collect Personal Information online from children under 13 without their parent’s consent except in special, limited circumstances, as described below. If a child is under 13 and wants to use the children’s sites with special activities, like scavenger hunts, personalized pages or clubs, the Company might ask the child to “register” by giving Us a first name and his/her state of residence. When asking for a child’s first name, the child is encouraged to use a “screen name” (not his/her real name) that only the child knows. Sometimes the child will be asked to make up a special password so that only they can see their customized areas on the site.

With parent’s verifiable consent, the Company may collect personal information from a child such as an e-mail address when the information is necessary for a particular activity. Usually the child is asked for his/her parent’s email in order to get parental permission for a child to provide any Personal Information. When We ask for parental permission, We will tell the parents what We will do with the information his/her child provides Us, and We will tell parents how they can review their child’s information and ask Us to delete the information. We do not keep parents’ (or children’s) e-mail address unless parents tell Us it is okay.

The Company might collect some information from a child under 13 without the parent’s consent, but only in the following special cases: If a child under 13 sends a request to Us, We keep their e-mail address for long enough to respond to them. The Company deletes this information from its system after the child’s question is answered. The Company’s webmaster is the only person who receives, collects or maintains children’s submitted information, even temporarily, through the Site. The webmaster will not use such information for any purpose, including marketing back to the child. The webmaster will not disclose information collected from children to third parties.

Occasionally, the Company has special site activities or promotions like sweepstakes or contests which are open to children even if they are under 13. In these activities, the Company is not allowed to ask for more information from a child other than what is necessary for a child to participate in the activity. For instance, the Company might ask for a parent’s email address so the Company can request information on how to send the child any prizes won or to tell a parent when his/her child has won a prize.

In the last two situations when the Company asks for information without parental consent, the Company requires the child to give his/her parent’s e-mail address, so the parent is notified that their child registered in a promotion or for a service. Any information a child provides in the above special circumstances will be deleted from the database once the promotion, program or activity is concluded, and after any legally required period for keeping such information is complete.

The Company also might collect contact information where it is necessary to protect a child’s safety. A parent can always ask to review the information his/her child has submitted by sending an email to [heycanes@raisingcanes.com](mailto:heycanes@raisingcanes.com) or a written request addressed to the Company, 400 Convention Street, Suite 550, Baton Rouge, LA 70802, Attention: Webmaster, Children’s Online Privacy Act – Information Request, or by calling the webmaster at 225-383-7400. Requests must include the screen name of the child, the child’s password and any other information which will allow the Company to verify that the requester is the parent of the child whose information is requested. A parent can ask to delete a child’s information at any time and a parent can ask that the Company not collect any more personal information from his/her child, by sending an email at [heycanes@raisingcanes.com](mailto:heycanes@raisingcanes.com) or a written request addressed to the Company 400 Convention Street, Suite 550, Baton Rouge, LA 70802, Attention: Webmaster, Children’s Online Privacy Act – Delete Request or by calling the webmaster at 225-383-7400.

BACK TO TOP

#### 10\. How do I contact the Company?

If you have any further questions concerning the Company’s Privacy Policy and the use of your Personal Information, please contact [heycanes@raisingcanes.com](mailto:heycanes@raisingcanes.com).

BACK TO TOP

#### 11\. What is your Mobile Privacy Policy?

Raising Cane's Restaurants, LLC ("Raising Cane's" or "We") respects your privacy and is committed to protecting it through our compliance with this policy. This policy describes:

  * The types of information we may collect or that you may provide when you text to enter a Contest (a "Text-to-Win Contest" or a "Contest"); and
  * Our practices for collecting, using, maintaining, protecting and disclosing that information.

This policy applies only to information we collect in a Text-to-Win Contest. This policy DOES NOT apply to information that:

  * We may collect offline or on any Raising Cane’s websites.
  * You provide to or is collected by any third party.

Our website has its own privacy policies, which we encourage you to read before providing information on or through it.

Please read this policy carefully to understand our policies and practices regarding your information and how we will treat it. If you do not agree with our policies and practices, do not text us to enter a Contest. By texting us, you agree to this privacy policy. This policy may change from time to time. Your continued use of texting to enter a Contest after we make changes is deemed to be acceptance of those changes, so please check the policy periodically for updates.

_Children under the Age of 13_

Entering a Contest via text message is not intended for children under 13 years of age, and we do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. If we learn we have collected or received personal information from a child under 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information. If you believe we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us at [heycanes@raisingcanes.com](mailto:heycanes@raisingcanes.com).

_Information We Collect and How We Collect It_

We collect information directly from you when you provide it to us via text message.

_Information You Provide to Us._

If you text us to enter a Contest, or are chosen as a potential winner of a Contest that you texted to enter, we may ask you to provide the following information:

  * **Personal Information.** Information by which you may be personally identified, such as name, date of birth, postal address, e-mail address, and/or telephone number

If you do not want us to collect this information, do not text to enter a Contest or, if you have already texted us, you may opt out at any time by texting STOP to the number you texted to enter.

_How We Use Your Information_

We use information that we collect about you or that you provide to us, including any personal information, to:

  * Contact you regarding the Contest.
  * Fulfill any other purpose for which you explicitly provide it.
  * Carry out our obligations and enforce our rights arising from any contracts entered into between you and us.

_Disclosure of Your Information_

We may disclose aggregated information about our users, and information that does not identify any individual, without restriction.

In addition, we may disclose personal information that we collect or you provide:

  * To our subsidiaries and affiliates.
  * To contractors, service providers and other third parties we use to support our business.
  * To a buyer or other successor in the event of a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution or other sale or transfer of some or all of our assets, whether as a going concern or as part of bankruptcy, liquidation or similar proceeding, in which personal information held by us about consumers who text to win a Contest is among the assets transferred.
  * To fulfill the purpose for which you provide it.
  * For any other purpose disclosed by us when you provide the information.
  * With your consent.
  * To comply with any court order, law or legal process, including to respond to any government or regulatory request.
  * If we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to protect the rights, property, or safety of Raising Cane's, our Customers or others. [This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.]

_Your California Privacy Rights_

California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits consumers who are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an e-mail to [heycanes@raisingcanes.com](mailto:heycanes@raisingcanes.com) or write us at: 6800 Bishop Rd., Plano, TX 75024.

_Data Security_

We have implemented measures designed to secure your personal information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, alteration and disclosure.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via mobile platforms is not completely secure. Although we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of your personal information transmitted via texting. Any transmission of personal information is at your own risk.

_Changes to Our Privacy Policy_

We may update our privacy policy from time to time. If we make material changes to how we treat our users' personal information, we will post the new privacy policy on this page with a notice that the privacy policy has been updated. The date the privacy policy was last revised is identified at the top of the page.

_Contact Information_

To ask questions or comment about this privacy policy and our privacy practices, contact us at: [heycanes@raisingcanes.com](mailto:heycanes@raisingcanes.com)

BACK TO TOP

NOTICE REGARDING FRANCHISE OFFERS OR SALES

None of the communications made through this Website should be construed as an offer to sell any franchise in, nor is any such communication directed to, the residents of any jurisdiction requiring registration of the franchise before it is offered or sold in the jurisdiction. No franchises will be sold to any resident of any such jurisdiction until the offer has been exempted from the requirements of, or duly registered in and declared effective by, such jurisdiction and the required Franchise Disclosure Document (if any) has been delivered to the prospective franchisee before the sale in compliance with applicable law. If you have any questions concerning the registration status of franchises in your jurisdiction, please contact [heycanes@raisingcanes.com](mailto:heycanes@raisingcanes.com) or call 1.866.55.CANES.
